# FKATERINA GLOAGUEN VASILEVA



+33 7 66 23 90 50

ek.gloaguen.vasileva@icloud.com



2 13 Rue Danton, 29200 Brest,

## FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a passionate web developer with over 3 years of IT industry working experience (including 2+ years of IT recruiting) and a strong scientific background in Biology and Cognitive Psychology.

My top-notch communication skills, commitment to staying up-to-date on the latest IT skills and industry knowledge, and dedication to excellence, creativity, and innovation make me a highly skilled and reliable developer.

My unique perspective and deep understanding of the field would make a valuable contribution to your team. I'd be delighted to discuss how we can work together to achieve your goals.

### PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

**LARAVEL 9**, 2023

SYMFONY 6 Udemy, 2022

**PHP7** Udemy, 2022

WEB DEVELOPMENT Udemy, 2022

PYTHON Coursera, 2021

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### PHP WEB DEVELOPER

back-end of different web Development of the applications (cms) using:

**PHP 8+** 

Laravel 8

PostgreSQL/MySQL

Git

Data Sfera

recruits

December 2022 - currently

IT RECRUITER (travel tech)

tech and soft skills interview,

www.sputnik8.com

2018 - 2020

### EDUCATION

#### **MASTER MARINE BIOLOGY**

The University of Naples Federico II 2021 Naples, Italy

#### **MASTER of PSYCHOLOGY**

Saint Petersburg State University 2017 Saint Petersburg, Russia

#### **BACHELOR of BIOLOGY**

Saint Petersburg State University 2015 Saint Petersburg, Russia

**MASTER PSYCHOLOGY THESIS PROJECT** 

junior developers and QA engineers tutoring

Search and assessment of potential candidates,

Scientific research, Academic writing, research project using Python, Data analysis using Statistica & R Saint Petersburg State University

The company has grown 2.5 times, with more than 30 new

2016 - 2017

#### **ASSISTANT WEBMASTER**

WordPress Realization of new sales support tools FX-PR.com 2015 - 2016

### SKILLS

- PHP
- Symfony 6
- Laravel 9,10
- JavaScript
- PostgreSQL/MySQL
- Git
- Python
- Statistica
- WordPress

### LANGUAGES

• English: C1

• French: C1

• Italian : A2

• Russian : Native